http://www.ucmtl.ca/privacy-policy

Children & Youth
What is RE?
Menu
Privacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletters.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:- To improve the user experience  (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)- To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company or organization for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.- To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your request or order.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email in compliance with CASL (Canadian Anti-Spam Legislation).How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and who are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information).We use cookies compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on Jul 12, 2014.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:communications@ucmtl.ca
Name
*
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
*
Thank you!
Unitarian Church of Montreal5035 boulevard de Maisonneuve O.Montreal, QC  H4A 1Y5 514-485-9933, office@ucmtl.ca Webmaster: communications@ucmtl.ca                     Privacy Policy - Terms of Service - FB PolicyThe content of this website is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.
